The Falconer is a documentary film directed by Annie Kaempfer.
This intimate portrait film follows master falconer Rodney Stotts on his mission to build a
bird sanctuary and to provide access to nature for his stressed community.
The Falconer weaves his present-day mission with the story of his past, both of which
are deeply rooted in issues of social and environmental injustice.
Stotts’s worldview in a nutshell: nature heals.
In a forgotten corner of our nation’s capital, he takes the time to break through to those too often dismissed as “hard to reach.” This is a story of second chances:
for injured birds of prey, for an abandoned plot of land, for a group of teenagers who have dropped out of high school, and for the falconer himself.
himself, played by Rodney Stotts.
Dangerous is a 2021 action thriller film directed by David Hackl and starring Scott
Eastwood, Tyrese Gibson, Famke Janssen, Kevin Durand, and Mel Gibson.
The film was released on November 5, 2021.
It was David Hackl's fifth film as director.
Dangerous was produced by Kevin DeWalt, Ben DeWalt and Doug Falconer under the banners of Mind's Eye Entertainment and Falconer
Pictures; and marks the last film of Falconer as a producer - he suddenly died in July 2021 before the release of the film.
The film was distributed in the United States and
the United Kingdom by Lionsgate.
It received negative reviews from critics for its plot and action.
The tone is thought_provoking.